Welcome to the World of Revolution,
a dating sim set at the Royal Academy
with three princes to choose from.
But there's only one character I'd
choose, and that's Miss Claire!
I'm in love with you and
I don't care who knows it!
Claire Francois,
the spoiled bossy rich
girl who torments the hero
until her plans blow up
in her face at the end?
That's right, I'm in
love with the villainous.
I want only you! Who said? that you want?
To restoration a lot.
You are too
selfish.
It's not so evil.
In-on
-one, No, no, no, no.
If the
emotions of something defensively, I can't
believe it.
What is it?
I know!
Your mind is strong.
What is it? I know!
I can't do it, you have to dream.
Reign your hands.
with your hands.
Reign your hands, one more time.
Reign your hands,
a good world.
I won't let you die until you die.
It's interesting, I love you.
But playing my favorite game
at night helped me de-stress.
Or so I thought.
How deplorable!
You can't expect someone like me to
sit in class with someone like this!
But then, suddenly...
You conceived attempt at humor?
Lift up your head and face me at once!
Excuse me!
Are you listening?
I opened my eyes and there she was.
I told you to stand up!
I refuse to share a desk with a commoner.
You need to learn your place.
Claire, is that you?
How dare you!
Addressing me by name alone as
though you've earned that right!
Wait, right over there.
What's happening?
Where am I?
This is just like the game.
Sorry, Miss Claire.
Was that so hard?
You must always remember the
proper way to address your betters.
I will, trust me.
And you remember my name, right?
Are you trying to insult me?
Ray Taylor?
Taylor's the family name of the game's
protagonist and Ray's the username I chose.
I seriously might pass out?
If this means what I think it does, then
have I been reincarnated in another world?
I love you. Huh?
I said I'm in love with you
and I don't care who knows it!
What? What?
Unhand me, you miscreant!
Have you gone completely mad?
I don't think so.
I am crazy in love with you, if
that's what you're asking me.
Honestly, do you think you
can curry favor with me?
I'm a noble.
No flowery words of love will soften
my disdain for a mere commoner.
Aw, you're so adorable!
Sorry, was that all loud?
Guess I got carried away.
By how ridiculously adorable
you are, that is! What?
Who exactly are you, anyway?
Someone you hate.
Isn't that right, Miss Claire? Yes.
I thought I had made that obvious.
I am 100 % okay with that!
In fact, you should keep
the bullying coming!
Please! I love it!
Y-Whaaa?
What a totally awesome start to a
super fun-filled school year, Ms.
Claire!
I'll make sure you enjoy
every moment with me!
I cannot imagine why you would assume I'd
want to associate with
you at all after today!
Ah!
Ray!
Oh, my.
How silly of me.
The way you were just staring off into
space, I thought you were part of the decor.
Miss Claire?
What do you want?
I hope you're not expecting an apology.
That was incredible!
You've got your minions,
but you're so independent,
you pick on your targets yourself!
Way to totally subvert the bully
stereotype, you are so brave!
What are you even talking about?
I mentioned I love you, because I do!
Oh, no.
I thought it was an ugly bug,
but it was just your shoe.
Harder.
I beg your pardon, commoner.
If you have something you want
to say to me, then speak clear.
I said if you're gonna step
on me, then do it harder!
Come on, I can feel you hesitating.
Show me some muscle.
You've got no reason to hold back on me,
so put your foot where your mouth is.
Huh?
Wait, what happened to my book?
Oh, how sad.
Dad, are you so poor that you can't
afford even a single textbook?
I'm so sorry, Ms. Claire.
I was too stupid to see
what you were trying to do.
Well, it's about time
you learned your lesson,
you absolute - I can't believe
you wanted to sit next to me
in class so badly that you hid
my textbook to make it happen!
I mean, we're already safe neighbors,
but I don't mind scooting
closer so that we can share.
Sure!
You're making zero sense right now!
Honestly, Ray, I have no idea
what goes through your mind.
You just had to start the
year provoking people.
I can't say I'm surprised Miss
Claire's coming after you now.
I wouldn't say she's coming after me.
It's honestly more like
the other way around.
Listen, as your roommate, I
feel I owe you this morning.
Do not get on Miss Claire's
bad side this year.
Her family,
the House of Francois, is one of the most
prestigious families in the Bauer Kingdom.
If you upset her, there's
nothing she can't do to get even.
You worry way too much, Misha.
I'm from a ruined noble family.
Trust me, I know how these things work.
I get what you're saying.
But still, I love everything
about Miss Claire.
You love that she's a
self-serving princess?
How could anyone not fall for that wicked
gaggle she does when
she's being malicious?
She's my perfect evil queen
and I would die for her.
You truly are one twisted individual.
Here's the thing about Claire.
Even though she's a bully,
she only takes it so far.
She pushed me down in the
hallway where it was safe.
And she only hid my textbook.
She didn't throw it away.
See what I mean?
Please have faith in us, Miss Claire.
We would be more than happy to
take care of that commoner for you.
Absolutely not!
If I want her to submit to me, I'm more
than capable of making her do it on my own!
Even though everyone wants
to do favors for her,
Miss Claire would rather
bully others herself.
She's a proud person by nature.
She uses intimidation to
hide how fragile she can be.
I could never dislike her when
I understand who she really is.
Maybe it's that complexity that
makes her so irresistible to me.
Uh how unsurprising no
one wanted to be your
partner that seems to happen to you lowly
commoners a lot teacher it's okay miss
claire said she'll be my partner no i did not
you're so filthy i thought
you were a pile of mud
It has no touching!
I'm so cold, Miss Claire.
Please warm me up.
Miss Claire, why is
this flower in my spot?
Since it's my very first gift from you,
I'll press it so I can keep it always.
That is a weed, you utter moron!
Don't you think that maybe
you're being a bit too resilient?
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
I mean exactly that! That face!
Why on earth are you smiling
throughout my mistreatment?
Mistreatment?
You mean tough love?
Absolutely not!
Then what would you
call all this flirting?
How dare you speak to
me in anger, Ray Taylor?
Commoners must keep quiet and
devote themselves to hard labor!
But I am devoting myself to
the hardest labor of all.
The labor of love.
I can't take any more of
this girl! Yes, you can.
Don't you lose heart now, Miss Claire.
What doesn't kill you makes
you stronger, you know?
Wait!
Where are you going?
I guess it worked.
You're being so resistant
to her bullying that Miss
Claire is about to quit
bothering you altogether.
What?
Stop what I want!
What am I supposed to do if she
stops being mean to me, Misha?
I don't know.
I guess you could try becoming
someone she can't resist harassing.
Think about it.
If she's the kind of person who always has
to be the best and in
control of everything,
then...
That's it?
If I behave the way my
avatar would in the game,
then Miss Claire will get competitive.
And then she'll have no
choice but to attack me.
Then I'll get to be close
to her and she'll attack
me again and again and
round and round it goes.
Less than a week into the term, and I've
gotten to spend so much time with her.
This feels like a win-win.
Hello, Miss Claire!
How are you today?
Stop right there, commoner!
How dare you greet her with familiarity!
Miss Claire belongs to a
completely different world than...
Whoa, I'm sorry, but I'm not
interested in talking to our minions.
I just wanted to say good
day to you, Miss Claire.
Hello.
You embarrass yourself, commoner.
Strange that you'd think I'd
have anything to say to you.
Especially when you don't
understand that good
day is said when you
part ways with someone.
But you still talk to me
and you cared enough to
correct my mistake so that
I can be a better person.
I love you.
I've had enough of this from you!
You've been mocking me for days now!
These ridiculous jokes aren't funny!
You've become quite the
eyesore on this campus.
I suggest you leave.
Ladies, please.
It's too early to be making so much noise.
I totally forgot the object of the
game is to date the three princes.
I couldn't be less interested.
That's the first prince, Rod Bauer.
The second prince, Thane Bauer.
And of course, Few
Bauer, the third prince.
The Three Princes of Bower Kingdom,
which is where we are now,
and they're here because they're the
actual romance routes in the game.
So what's going on?
You having fun without me?
Seems pretty rude of you.
Oh no, Prince Rod!
We weren't having any fun
whatsoever, I promise you!
I was just shooing away
a filthy little pest
who was trying to bring
disorder to this academy.
Sorry, my hearing's not great.
Did you say you wanted to
get disorderly with me?
I most certainly did not!
Ray Taylor, wasn't it?
Good to finally meet the
highest-ranking new student.
Are you friends?
Um, yes, Prince Yu.
We went to the same elementary school.
She's certainly different from the
noble girls we usually see around here.
Gotta hand it to Dad.
His new merit-based admissions policy is
turning out some pretty hilarious results.
Thane!
Care to say hello?
No, thank you.
Hello, Prince Thane.
Hey, Miss Claire!
Why don't you go over
there and talk to him?
Why would you suggest something like that?
Oh, I think you know why.
It's true.
The one Miss Claire actually has
feelings for is Prince Over-It Thane.
You like him.
What an absolutely preposterous idea!
Shut your impudent mouth at once!
Oops. It slipped out.
Look at how cute she is when
she's all mad and blustered.
No!
You are so wrong!
I have no interest whatsoever in
vying for Prince Thane's favor!
Uh, um, please forgive
me, I didn't mean to -
Uh...
Hear that, Thane?
You got rejected by a girl
without even pursuing her.
Oh man, I'm striking out
left and right today.
Poor Thane.
He's so dark and gloomy,
but I imagine it's hard not to be when
you're always in your brother's shadow.
He obviously is super insecure
about it, and because of that,
he's not the easiest person to talk to.
I don't have a problem with him, though.
You wretch!
How could you do that?
Now you've upset Prince Thane!
Then let's go and apologize to him.
He's a very sensitive guy, after all.
How would a commoner like you know
what a prince like him is feeling?
And why should I apologize with you?
Come on, we can do this.
This is none of your concern!
I will not stand for it.
If you insist on behaving like
this you leave me no choice
but to bully you mercilessly
until you cry and beg me to stop!
Prepare yourself Ray Taylor I will
absolutely never leave you alone.
Water wasn't enough to
deter her then I'll dump
tea on her instead no
boiling liquid might be too?
much.
Miss Claire, maybe you should just put
that commoner out of your mind for now?
She honestly seems to enjoy being bullied,
which is unsettling to say the least.
I'll give up when I'm ready!
Hold on, are you studying?
Well, yes, because our exams are tomorrow.
All right, don't remind me.
Seriously, who gives exams
a week into the school year?
That's what I'll do Ray Taylor.
Let's see which of us performs
better on tomorrow's exams.
If my scores are higher then you're to
remove yourself from this academy at once.
Uh no thanks I don't
want to well you could at
least think it over
before making a decision.
But why there's nothing I stand to gain so
why would I want to
compete besides if I left
the Academy that would
mean I wouldn't be able
to mess around with you
anymore stop I do not
care for your phrasing
the idea of you messing
around with me could
be Taken the wrong way
there is no reason to
back down unless the top
ranked new Student isn't
prepared you have a good
point let's do this Miss Claire but if You
don't win that means I
do and you'll have to do
one thing I ask of you
Really and what makes
you think I would agree
is there a reason you're
backing Away the academy's
top student isn't
prepared are you trying
to provoke me Ray Taylor
very Well then I accept
your terms Misha you
ready you will be our
witness for this competition
Is that all right with
you Ray of course it is
Then make your vows I
swear in the name of god.
Culture, history, literature.
Subjects unrelated to everyday life
are where we nobles reign supreme.
In other words, I have an
overwhelming advantage.
That little plebeian is doomed.
You may now begin your exams.
Oh, that's right.
I remember doing this.
After all the hours I spent
grinding in this game,
I've already completed this
exam event several times.
The exams are easy, especially
for fans of the game.
They become a go-to way
to score extra points.
Okay, well, the table manners
part was easier than the gameplay.
All I had to do was answer
multiple-choice questions.
I'm sure having the
skills naturally because
you've been doing it all
your life helps a lot.
The nobles definitely
have the advantage here.
Yikes!
She's way too beautiful!
I can't handle that dress!
It's too hot! I love her!
I want to burn this image into my retinas!
Point deduction for Ray Taylor.
First off, we shall assess your ability.
Second, we will examine
your use of magic tools.
In the basic magic exam,
we will be evaluating your
attributes as well as your aptitude
there are four attributes earth
water fire and wind in general
a person can possess only a
single attribute aptitude has
five levels exceptional high
intermediate low and non-existent
you're amazing miss claire high
aptitude the fire scale that's great
yes it is isn't it my what
a lively bunch they are
oh what did you just do dear i put my
hand over it those of you who have been
graded may now move
on to magic tools
you
look like you're having
a good time Rod hey
there you what's up done with your exams
yep all set and how is Thane doing
he's
in a bad mood today apparently he had a
hard time with the general curriculum exam
Next, Ray Taylor.
Hey, isn't that...
That's the girl we met with Misha earlier.
Wow, that was really well done.
Her aim may have been a little off the
mark, but she seems to have great intuition.
I don't know.
Something's up.
She moved it.
Fascinating.
He said her name's Ray Taylor.
Oh, rather unusual for you to
commit anyone's name to memory.
What can I say?
You must be so tired!
I'm interested in her.
I'm exhausted.
Commoner, what could you
possibly want at this hour?
After a full day of exams, I'm completely
worn out, both mentally and physically.
I'm replenishing my energy.
Come here?
Why,
Miss Claire,
you're glowing today.
I'm sure I don't know what you mean.
Lene, you are did something
especially good happen to you?
I'm just excited for the results of
our recent exams to be announced.
Oh goodness, commoner, you have
bags under your eyes. Gross.
You're so funny, Miss Claire.
Yeah, I hardly got any sleep last night.
How unfortunate for you.
Was it because you knew you
were going to lose today?
I probably wouldn't sleep
either if I were you.
Well, no.
I was actually trying to figure out
what I'd ask you to do when I win.
And before I knew it,
it was time to get up.
Oh,
you have quite some nerve,
students.
I will now announce your results.
First, the general curriculum exam.
I'm not surprised you and I
took the top two positions.
But not a bad showing, Rick.
Thank you.
That means a lot to me.
There must be some mistake.
How could I possibly score
lower than in a simple commoner.
I'm sorry, Ms.
Claire, what can I say?
I didn't just spend my
free time playing the game.
I also wrote an entire fanfic.
It's a story about Ms.
Claire falling from grace and then
rising back up to peak validity.
I needed to understand the game's world.
And the age in which it takes place,
So I read every book I
could find on the setting.
from cover to cover.
Frankly, I'm pretty sure I know more about
the game than the people who made it.
Moving on, next we have the
results of the etiquette exam.
There!
I knew that last one was just dumb luck.
Your mask has fallen and we can
see your true lack of intelligence.
Look how excited she is.
He's so cute.
And finally, the results
of the magic ability exam.
Now, the moment of truth.
Hope you packed your bags, commoner.
Oh!
First place, Ray Taylor!
Unmeasurable? But how?
Oh
Thank you so much for joining us.
I don't want to know if I can't do this.
I want to know if I can't do this?
Thank you.